<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome! on Alexandre</title>
    <link>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome! on Alexandre</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 4: Youtube Analysis</title>
      <link>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Youtube Analysis Project background and context This project aims to provide a comprehensive overview of a YouTube channel, with a focus on key metrics such as video performance, audience demographics, channel growth, video content analysis, trending topics, and a comparison with similar channels. The goal of this project is to provide insights into the channel&amp;rsquo;s strengths and areas for improvement, and to inform strategic decisions related to content creation, audience engagement, and monetization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: SpaceX - Winning the space race</title>
      <link>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>SpaceX - Winning the space race Project background and context
We have identified that for SpaceY be able to compete with Space X our client needs to know what are the best practices, the key parameter what the probability of the first stage to land successfully. Having a successful land of the first stage means saving almost 200 milion dollars. Problems you want to find answers
The project task is to predict what are the chances of the first stage to land successfully, and how the other components like payload, booster, and launch sites can impact on that chance, using SpaceX Falcon 9 as a model Methodologies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Credit Card Fraud Detection</title>
      <link>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Credit Card Fraud Detection Decision Tree and Support Vector Machine models were used to recognize fraudulent credit card transactions Comparison between Scikit-Learn and Snap efficiency. Libraries used on the project: Numpy Pandas Scikit-Learn Matplotlib Link to GitHub Repository</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: US Domestic AirLine Performance</title>
      <link>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Yearly airline performance report
For the chosen year provide,
Number of flights under different cancellation categories using bar chart. Average flight time by reporting airline using line chart. Percentage of diverted airport landings per reporting airline using pie chart. Number of flights flying from each state using choropleth map. Number of flights flying to each state from each reporting airline using treemap chart. Yearly average flight delay statistics
For the chosen year provide,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexsmaeda.github.io/Alex_Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these social media
Platform URL LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandre-maeda/ Github: https://github.com/alexsmaeda E-mail: alexandresmaeda@gmail.com </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
